http://www.durasupreme.com/privacypolicy

Dura Supreme Privacy Policy | Dura Supreme Cabinetry
The safety and well-being of our customers, employees and communities is our top priority. We have adapted and evolved our manufacturing processes to operate safely and be able to meet our delivery commitments. - Learn More
Skip to main content
Showroom Locator
Products
Style + Design
Storage
Getting Started
AboutContact Us
Sustainability
Warranty
Online Brochures
Press Room
Careers
Blog
Dura Supreme Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Dura Supreme, Inc. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.durasupreme.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Dura Supreme.
Personal Identification Information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, company name, referal source, and in some cases a customer code, business size, type and volume. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-Personal Identification Information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web Browser Cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How We Use Collected Information
Dura Supreme may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
- To improve customer serviceInformation you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
- To personalize user experienceWe may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
- To improve our SiteWe may use feedback you provide and/or your activity to improve our products, services and website.
- To process paymentsWe may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service (for example we may provide information to one of our contracted sales rep agencies/agent to help provide a higher level of customer service).
- To run a promotion, contest, survey or other featureTo send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
- To send periodic emailsWe may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order or shipment. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site or email service provider.
How We Protect Your Information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site, email service providers, and secured internal database/software.
Sharing your Personal Information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys and providing service. For example our advertising & communication partners (e.g. Googel Analytics, Constant Contact, AddThis) or our contracted Sale Representation agencies/agents. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.
Third Party Websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, authorized dealers/showrooms, sales rep agencies/agents, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies. If you visit a Website that is linked to our Website, you should consult that Website's privacy policy before providing any personal information.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
Dura Supreme has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your Acceptance of These Terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
User Submitted Content/Media Policy
Dura Supreme welcomes your comments and other communications, photos, videos, or any other content that you submit to Dura Supreme’s website or share through various formats (including social media platforms, email, private messaging apps, and more), and that you allow Dura Supreme to feature, such as your name, social media handle, business name, photographer detials, accompanying text, and any images from your social media accounts (e.g. Twitter™, Instagram™, Pinterest™, Facebook, Houzz) (collectively, "User Content") as long as the User Content submitted by you complies with these Terms & Conditions as well as Dura Supreme’s General Review Writing Guidelines, which are incorporated into these Terms & Conditions in their entirety. To learn more about and respond to our User Submitted Content/Media Policy, CLICK HERE >
Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
Dura Supreme, Inc.www.durasupreme.com300 Dura Drive Howard Lake, MN 55070888-711-3872marketing@durasupreme.com
300 Dura DriveHoward Lake, MN 55349t: (320) 543-3872f: (800) 242-3872
Kitchen Remodeling: Time to Go Kitchen A...
Sep 29, 2020
Get the Look: Scandinavian Style Kitchen...
Sep 15, 2020
Kitchen Design: Cooking with Gas or Elec...
